{
    "subject": "resource/Robert_Mundell",
    "predicate": "ontology/award",
    "object": "resource/Nobel_Memorial_Prize_in_Economic_Sciences",
    "human_readable": "Robert Mundell won the Nobel Memorial Prize in Economic Sciences.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9861080050468445,
            "question": "When did Robert Mundell likely win the Nobel Memorial Prize in Economic Sciences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9350259900093079,
            "question": "Who won the Nobel Memorial Prize in Economic Sciences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8398523330688477,
            "question": "Who else has won the Nobel Memorial Prize in Economic Sciences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8242256045341492,
            "question": "In what field did Robert Mundell receive a Nobel Prize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8172969818115234,
            "question": "What prize did Robert Mundell win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7976430654525757,
            "question": "What is the significance of winning the Nobel Memorial Prize in Economic Sciences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7093535661697388,
            "question": "What is the full name of the prize Robert Mundell won?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6311871409416199,
            "question": "Name a major economic theory associated with Robert Mundell."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6131274700164795,
            "question": "What are some of Robert Mundell's key contributions to economics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3377981185913086,
            "question": "What are some current debates in economics that relate to Mundell's work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robert Mundell won the Nobel Memorial Prize in Economic Sciences.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8638_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Robert Mundell's key contributions to economics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8638_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a major economic theory associated with Robert Mundell.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8638_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the full name of the prize Robert Mundell won?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8638_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8638_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8638_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8638_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8638_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8638_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8638_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8638_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8638_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8638_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8638_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the required format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}